federalnewsnetwork.com 2019-08-14

# Hubbard Radio – Privacy Policy

_Updated: May  2018_

**Any users located within the European Economic Area (“EEA”) are prohibited from using our Platforms.   For avoidance of doubt, the Hubbard Radio Platforms are not intended for users located within the EEA. **

This is the Privacy Policy for the Hubbard Radio, LLC subsidiaries’ websites and mobile apps (“Platforms”) operated by Hubbard Radio, LLC’s subsidiaries.  Your privacy is important to us, and we provide this Privacy Policy regarding our online collection, use and disclosure practices to help you to make informed decisions regarding use of our Platforms, and exercising choices regarding our collection, use and disclosure of your personal information on our Platforms.

This Privacy Policy is incorporated by reference into and is subject to the [Hubbard Radio, LLC Terms of Use](https://corporate.hubbardradio.com/terms-of-use/).

**The Information We Collect**

While using our Platforms, you may review content, enter our various sweepstakes and contests, or link to our Facebook, Twitter or Instagram pages by liking or following us, along with a variety of other functions. In providing these offerings on our Platforms, we  _may_  collect: your name, birth date, gender, email address, zip code, and any other information you may submit to us (for example: your street address or telephone number). We gather this information in a variety of ways, such as when you email us, fill out a user profile, register on our web or mobile app stream, or enter a sweepstakes or contest. We may also ask you to create a personal password when you register for one of our products or services. We also collect certain non-personally identifiable information whenever you visit our website, such as the type of browser you are using (for example: Chrome, Safari, etc.), the type of operating system you are using (for example: Windows or Mac OS), the domain name from which you receive Internet access, and aggregate information regarding what pages you access or visit.

**Collection of Information by Third Party Sites, Sale Partners and Sponsors**

Some of our Platforms contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. We encourage you to consult these other sites’ privacy policies, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. To try to bring you advertising that is of interest to you, we have relationships with reputable third parties that we allow to present or serve advertisements on our Platforms. Ad server companies may collect information about your use of our Platforms such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. Our Privacy Policy does not cover any use of information that a third party ad server may collect from you. We sometimes may offer content (for example: contests, sweepstakes, or promotions) that is sponsored by or co-branded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, these third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that you voluntarily submit to participate in the activity. We have no control over such third parties’ use of any information you provide to them.

To opt out of interest-based advertising, visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org/ _choices_](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/)  or [http://www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) for desktop and mobile websites. To opt out of interest-based advertising on mobile apps, see your mobile device carrier.

**Our Use of Information Collected on Our Platforms and Your Choices Regarding that Use**

We may use the personally identifiable information that we collect to provide you with an interactive online experience, to fulfill your requests for our products and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, to notify you when we make changes to our subscriber agreements, to personalize or localize your experience on our Platforms, to allow us to make personalized recommendations of content you may be interested in, or to contact you about your account with us.  We may, on occasion, combine information we receive online from you with records from other sources. As provided in our [Terms](https://corporate.hubbardradio.com/terms-of-use/) of Use, if you choose to post content on our Platforms, we may use that information in any manner. In addition, we may use the personally identifiable information we collect through our Platforms to offer you other programs, services or products that we believe may be of interest to you. If you do not want to receive e-mail offers from us in the future, please let us know by unsubscribing to any email at the bottom of each of our email messages. Please allow time for your request to be implemented. We use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our Platforms and to enable us to personalize your online experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze usage, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services.

**Cookies and Other Technical Information**

We send “cookies” to your computer, mobile device, or tablet primarily to enhance your online experience and to store visitor preferences, record session information, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, alert visitors to new areas that we think might be of interest to them when they return to our Platforms, record past activity on our Platforms in order to provide better service when visitors return to our Platforms, ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same display advertising, customize content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends. Cookies are files that can identify you as a unique customer and store your personal preferences as well as technical information (including click through and click stream data). Cookies can either be permanent (that is, they remain on your computer until you delete them) or temporary (that is, they last only until you close your browser).

We may also use “Web beacons” that monitor your use of our Platforms. Web beacons are small strings of code that provide a method for delivering a display advertisement on a webpage for the purpose of transferring data, such as the IP (Internet Protocol) address of the device that downloaded the page on which the Web beacon appears, the URL (Uniform Resource Locator) of the page on which the Web beacon appears, the time the page containing the Web beacon was viewed, the types of browser that fetched the Web beacon and the identification number of any cookie on the device previously placed by that server. When corresponding with you via HTML-capable e-mail, Web beacons let us know whether you received and opened our e-mail.

We also use Remarketing with Google to advertise online. Third-party vendors, including Google, may show you our ads on websites across the Internet. We and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on someone’s past visits to our Platforms.

If you have installed an app on your mobile device or tablet and you wish to stop receiving push notifications, you can change the settings either on your device or through the app.

If you choose to furnish one of our Platforms with personally identifiable information, this information can be stored in or linked to other data stored in the cookies/Web beacons. By accepting this Privacy Policy, you specifically agree to our use of cookies and Web beacons as described herein.

You may adjust your browser to reject cookies from us or from any other website. Additionally, by setting your Web browser to display HTML e-mails as text only, you may be able to prevent the use of some Web beacons. Please consult the “Help” section of your browser for more information. However, there is certain information on our Platforms that can only be accessed in conjunction with cookies or similar devices and you should be aware that disabling cookies or similar devices might prevent you from accessing some of our content or otherwise impair, prevent, or diminish certain functionality of our Platforms.

**Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information**

We try to limit our disclosures of personally identifiable information that our users have not posted on our Platforms to those that are important to carrying on our business. For example, if you choose to post content on our website (for instance: “comment on a story”), we may freely disclose that content to others, and may also freely disclose any other information you have provided to us, other than personally identifiable information.We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to a legal process–for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose personally identifiable information in response to a law enforcement agency’s request or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law. In addition, we may transfer information about you if we are acquired by or merged with another company, or if our assets are acquired by another entity. Agents and contractors of Hubbard Radio and its subsidiaries who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy by, for example, not using personally identifiable information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for us.

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.

**Our Commitment to Security**

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access to personally identifiable information, maintain data security, and to insure that use of personally identifiable information is in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**Notice Regarding Changes to this Policy**

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in this Privacy Policy. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Platforms to notify you of these changes, together with a new date at the top of the Privacy Policy, and will provide you with the ability to opt-out of these new uses by visiting the Contact page of the applicable Platforms you provided information through. Please note that there are certain service notifications that you may not opt-out of, such as notifications of changes to our products, services, or policies.

We encourage you to refer this Privacy Policy periodically and review the effective date at the top of the Privacy Policy to see if the Policy has changed, so that you are always current on our privacy practices pertaining to your information.

**Notice Regarding Nielsen Market Research and Measurements**

Our Platforms may feature Nielsen proprietary measurement software, which will allow you to contribute to market research, such as Nielsen Ratings. To learn more about the information that Nielsen software may collect and your choices with regard to it, see the Nielsen Digital Measurement Privacy Policy at <http://www.nielsen.com/digitalprivacy>. To opt-out or opt back into Nielson Measurement, [click here](http://www.nielsen.com/digitalprivacy).

**How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or its implementation you may write us at our postal address:

Hubbard Radio, LLC  
3415 University Avenue  
St. Paul, MN 55114  
Attn: Privacy Officer
